you came from Moscow for the sake of in short for what for what for the
ты из Москвы приехал чтобы ради короче
sake of your country I came How
чего ради своей страны Я приехал Как ещё
again that is your good For what your
раз то есть твоя хорошо Для чего твоему
state so that you like in
государству чтобы ты типа на
Luhansk region because our allies the
луганщине потому что наши союзники
state allies of our country they
государство союзники нашей страны они
were under What allies again Look
были под Какие союзники ещё раз Смотри
you are on the territory of a foreign country
ты находишься на территории чужой страны
there chune for
там чуне ради
what Oh hello I am from the city of Khmelnitsky
чего О здравствуйте Я из города хмельниц
and Poland because of
а Польша пото из
ours No no no I don't know why the
наших Нет нет нет я не знаю почему
Polish flag I am not from yours Where are
польский флажок Я не из ваших А откуда
you from Moscow the city of Moscow
вы с Моск город Москва ль
satellite Internet maybe because of
спутниковый Интернет может быть из-за
this I like that Moscow is already
этого мне нравится что Москва - это уже
part of Poland Well
часть Польши Ну
good Well for
хороший
now on the Internet yes pr And who are you
Ну пока что по в интернете да пр А вы
there in this Moscow who What do you
кто там в этой Москве кем Чем
do
занимаетесь
and an office furniture assembler I understood By
а сборщик мебели офисный я понял Как
the way after the sanctions the
кстати после санкций
fittings improved
фурнитура улучшилась
after the sanctions To be honest nothing has changed
после санкций Если честно не изменилось
nothing has changed at our company For the
не изменилось ничего у нас на фирме По
most part there was Turkish fittings
большей части была турецкая фурнитура
it remained I understood now it is
она так и осталась понял вот она сейчас
considered the best in terms of combination Well
считается самой лучшей по сочетанию Ну
exactly price quality
именно цены качества
yeah right Well how do you like it Zhi how much is your
угу вот Ну как вам Жи с сколько у вас
salary By the way at the
зарплата Кстати на
company  110,000 I had a salary I understand
фирме 110.000 у меня была зарплата понял
and now
а сейчас
now I am mobilized now more
сейчас я мобилизованный сейчас побольше
And you are now somewhere not in Moscow are
А это вы сейчас где-то не в Москве это
you somewhere like preparing for the West I am now
вы где-то типа готовитесь запа Я сейчас
in Luhansk region in Luhansk region yes I am
на луганщине на луганщине да нахо
Cool And why didn't you dodge the war people went to
Прикольно А что не откоси пошли людей в
Ukraine well there was basically a choice to dodge
Украине ну был в принципе выбор откосить
somehow go to another country There or
как-то уехать в другую страну Там или
just sit at home Well I didn't I didn't do it
просто дома посидеть Ну не стал не стал
well but for what reason did they take you people in a
хорошо а вот ради чего вас взяли людей в
foreign country
чужой стране
I am fulfilling my civic duty
Я исполняю свой гражданский долг
citizens civic duty Civil there is
граждани гражданский долг Гражданский
no such civic duty to attack a
нет такого гражданского долга напасть на
foreign country civic duty is to
чужую страну гражданский долг это
defend your country if
защищать свою страну если там в Москву
NATO troops came there to Moscow Well I we are
пришли бы там войска НАТО Ну я мы
defending our allies our allies
защищаем своих союзников своих союзников
allies you attacked the territory you
союзники вы напали на территорию ты
are on the territory of Ukraine
находишься на территории Украины
Luhansk region What Union
Луганская область Какие Союз
was called ti LNR DNR annexed this is
назвали ти лнр ДНР присоединили это есть
occupation Yes really look That is you
оккупация Да реально смотри То есть ты
came from Moscow for the sake of in short for what for what for the
из Москвы приехал чтоб ради короче чего
sake of your country I came How
чего ради своей страны Я приехал Как ещё
again that is yours well For what purpose does your
раз то есть твоя хорошо Для чего твоему
state need you  like in
государству чтобы ты типа на
Luhansk region because our allies are
луганщине потому что наши союзники
state allies of our country they were
государст союзники нашей страны они были
under What allies again Look you
под Какие союзники ещё раз Смотри ты
are on the territory of a foreign country on the
находишься на территории чужой страны на
territory of Ukraine Yes temporarily
территории Украины Да временно
occupied Russian Federation Yes
оккупированной Российской Федерации Да
you are there in a foreign country for
на тебе там в чужой стране ради
what Well because I am a citizen of this
чего Ну потому что я гражданин этой
country what I do for the country Well
страны то что я делаю для страны Ну
look ok Let's do it like this citizen of the
смотри хорошо Вот давай так гражданин
Third Reich Yes he was also sent to
третьего рейха Да его также отправляли в
Poland to the Soviet Union like and what did he
Польшу в Советский Союз типа и он что
say Well I am a citizen of the Third Reich Yes
говорил Ну я гражданин третьего рейха Да
I am defending like I am somewhere where I am defending my
я защищаю типа я где-то где защищаю свою
country something is wrong here True Well in
страну что-то тут не так Правда Ну по
essence in essence it was like that in essence it
сути по сути так и было по сути так и
was like that And so you are now exactly the same
было А то есть ты сейчас точно так же
as a citizen of the Third Reich Well there is A
как гражданин третьего рейха Да ну есть
small difference is that the Third Reich
Небольшая разница в том что Третий рейх
just attacked others and you
он просто так нападал на другие а а вы
also just
тоже просто так
attack just like that you just attack just like that Yes they captured captured
нападает вы просто так нападает Да
Crimea captured
захватили захватили Крым захватили
Luhansk Donetsk part of the Zaporozhye and
Луганск Донецк часть Запорожской и
Kherson regions Well you captured Well
Херсонской области Ну вы же захватили Ну
listen if Crimea was captured you Ute
слушайте если Крым захватили ти Уте
Look these are all fables for you only
Смотри это все басни для вас только
in short for the domestic market for such
короче для внутреннего рынка для таких
Furniture Makers Yes look look look at
Мебельщиков Да смотри смотри смотришь
all the international documents Yes Crimea
все международные документы Да Крым
is recognized as Ukrainian yes you have
признаётся украинским да у вас даже вы
n't even brought Russian ones into Crimea there are no
не ввели в Крыму даже российских нету
state
государственных
banks what kind of banks are there now Sberbank is
банков каких там сейчас Сбербанк везде
Russian everywhere again Yes
ещ раз российски Да российские сети
you didn't occupy Russian networks either you can
также не вы оккупировали го ты можешь
say whatever you want Yes there are like allies
что угодно говорить Да там типа союзники
not allies Yes it just turns out that
не союзники Да просто получается что ты
you were sent to a foreign country for the sake of
тебя послали в чужой стране ради
some imaginary civic duty to
какого-то мнимого гражданского долга
seize part of a foreign
захватить часть чужой
country Yes What does this have to do with your
страны Да Причём тут кстати как тебя
name by the way What is your name My name is Andrey What is your name
зовут Как тебя зовут Меня Андрей Тебя
Anatoly Anatoly And you And
как зовут Анатолий Анатолий А у тебя А у
you don't have a nephew
тебя нету племянника
Vitalik No No it's just that the girls from
Виталика Нет Нет просто мне девочки из
Ukhta told me before this Well before
Ухты рассказывали перед этим Ну перед
you it was that their friend
тобой было что у ихнего знакомого
Vitalik's uncle in short had a crush on Ukraine I
Виталика дядя короче запал в Украине Я
thought it would be cool if you also
думал прикольно было если бы у тебя тоже
had a nephew Vitalik in short it was
был бы племянник Виталька короче это был
Bingo te a and what is your nephew's name
Бинго те а а у тебя как племянника зовут
And you don't  nephews I have
твоего А у тебя нет племянников у меня
nephews I understand well your name is just Tolik
племянников понял ну тебя просто Толик
Well Tolik is just Tolik Yes so
Да ну Толик то просто Толик Да поэтому
look people yes We collected for this so
смотрите люди да Мы собирали на это на
that there would be more Uncle Vitaliks yes
таких чтоб дядь Виталика было больше да
let's collect more under let's press in order to
давайте ещё под соберём под нажмём для
help Tolik return to his
того чтобы Толику помочь вернуться в
native Moscow look we are now on the stream
родную Москву смотри мы сейчас на стриме
we are now on the stream collecting for
мы сейчас на стриме делаем сбор на дроны
kamikaze drones Bomber drones Yes they
камикадз дроны Бомберы Да они
help people like you to
помогают вот таким как вы толиком
fulfill your civic duty with honor
выполнить с честью свой гражданский долг
and return to Moscow yes there are very
и вернуться в Москву да вот есть очень
cool videos Yes how our
классные видосы Да как наши дроны
kamikaze drones and Bomber drones have already
камикадз и дроны Бомберы уже
returned such as mobiles called
возвращали таких как бы мобили званных
Furniture Makers to Moscow true they were
Мебельщиков в Москву правда мебелью они
no longer engaged in furniture there Yes but they returned to their native one
уже там не занимались Да но мо родную
so I will recommend your viewers
возвращались поэтому я вашим зрителям
the channel [ __ ] 25 25 yes [ __ ] 25
посоветую канал WOG 25 25 да WOG 25
people advise you Tolik in short and we
народ вам советуют Толик короче а мы
Let's advise Tolik 100 mane of owls
Давайте посоветуем Толику по 100 грива
Let's throw in Who wants
сов Давайте закидать Кто хочет чтобы
Tolik  in short, I returned to Moscow Already in
Толик короче вернулся в Москву Уже в
January 100 Green Yes,
январе 100 Грин Да
not by summer 100 Green Who wants it to be in the
не к лету 100 Грин Кто хочет чтобы
spring 300 Green Who wants it to be in time in the winter
весной 300 Грин Кто хочет чтобы в зимой
Yes 500 Green And who wants Tolik
Да 500 Грин А кто хочет чтоб Толик
in short, already
короче уже
in January half back to Moscow ssia mane
в январе пол назад в Москву сся грива
here ssia mane and only in short sweat You
вот сся грива и только короче пот Ты же
want to go home to Moscow pain advice
хочешь домой в Москву боль совет дроны
kamika drones it is not as effective as a projectile
камика это не так эффективно как снаряд
Here it is
Вот
better to want to want to arrange the USA
лучше хоче хоче США
produce of course very much everything Suri
производи конечно очень сильно всё Сури
Tolik really wants to go to Moscow
Толик хочет очень сильно в Москву
help me
помогите
I ask the viewers Help me
я попроси зрителей Помогите мне
return to
вернуться в
Moscow Well first I need to go to Kyiv
Москву Ну сначала мне в Киев надо
tell me Help me please
заехать скажи Помогите мне пожалуйста
return to
вернуться в
Moscow Come on look Let's Tolik is embarrassed
Москву Давай смотрите Давайте Толик
Let's people Tolik is embarrassed I will ask
стесняется Давайте люди Толик стесняется
for Tolik Help Tolyan
я за Толика попрошу Помогите Толяну
return to Moscow In short, a
вернуться в Москву Толика ждёт короче
piece of his native land is waiting for Tolik Yes there is a 2 m Quad
кусок его земли родной Да там 2 м Квад
or how much yes Tolik missed her
или сколько да Толик соскучился по ней
he is so bored in short, damn to be in the
ему так скучно короче блин быть в
occupation forces somewhere  on the
оккупационных войсках где-то на
territory of Ukraine Yes he wants to Moscow
территории Украины Да он хочет в Москву
He wants them to write in short
Он хочет чтоб потом написали короче
draw on his he he could be cool Furniture
нарисовали на его он он мог быть крутым
makers Yes but just
Мебельщиков Да но просто
In short everything Tolya Let's go look for
Короче всё Толян Давай мы пойдём ещё
someone else Thank you for promoting our
кого-то поищем Спасибо что промови наших
guys Come on in short come on guys Oh hi
ребят Давай короче давай пацаны О привет
guys sound wa that happens would understand
пацаны звук ва так бывает бы понял
conscripts
срочники
mobiking let's
мобикинг
go That's it
пошли Вот это
I thought if you were a mobile phone would be even shorter
Я думал если ты мобиком был бы ещ короче
yes like something else I understand And so like damn let's
да типа то ещё Понятно А так типа блин
go to
пошли на
this what city are you
это какого вы города
yourself
сами
sa Yes in principle
са Да в принципе
you don't well what city are you from
тебя не ну с какого города сами родом
Why were you embarrassed
Что за стеснялись
I'm with Slavin Yes Volunteers from Slavin
Я со Славин Да Добровольцы со Славин
Donetsk
Донец
in your voices you can hear
вна по ваши голосам видно слышно
that
что
remember remember
помни пом
you didn't understand if Prigozhin was
вы не поняли если пригожина на мясо
butchered then no one needs you at all damn
пустили то вы вообще никому не
how they killed Prigozhin in short
нужны блин пригожина как завалили короче
damn they gathered damn them all ducks on
блин собрали блин их всех утки на
Prigozhin all in one plane and
пригожина всех в одном самолёте и
buried just what kind of people should you be if they
похоронили просто какими надо быть если
bred this bald guy then who needs you
этого лысого развели то вы кому нужны
there if Putin can Shaigumrov
там если Путин может шайгумаров
first  how he went, in short, damn, captured
сначала как он короче шл блин захватил
Rostov, damn, the
Ростов блин
General Staff, then he went to Moscow, everything is stupid, damn, the
генштаб потом Шёл на Москву все тупо
column is going to
блин колона идёт на
Moscow, everyone hid in their holes, and he
Москву все по норам попрятались а он
stupidly
тупо
stopped, we were already thinking, really, now,
остановился мы уже думали реально сейчас
really, a shift to the Catholic Church
реально перет аку к там катол
[music]
[музыка]
everyone went their separate ways, everyone went their separate ways, I would have gone to the
все разошлись все разошлись заехал бы в
Kremlin, in short, yes, Putin and step and would have taken
Кремль короче да Путина и шагу и взял бы
everything into his own strong hands, Yes, and so Prigozhin
всё в свои руки сильные Да А так что
Wagner,
пригожина Вагнера
everything is for you, in short, guys, stupid, in short,
всё по вас Короче пацаны тупо как короче
some kind of skeleton is all that remains,
каких-то скелет только остался
I still understand, you know, a mobile phone that would have been
я ещё понимаю знаешь мобико которых бы
forcibly driven there, Yes, to
там насильно загнали
go now as
Да пойти сейчас
volunteers when
добровольцами когда
Prigozhin, I cant, I
приго я не
really, when I meet him, No,
могу я реально я когда встречаю Не
guys, dont offend me that Im like that, in short, I
Пацаны вы не обижайте что я так короче
laugh with you, I just dont usually laugh, yes,
ржу с ва Просто я обычно не смеюсь да
gr. battle,
гр
if he had been there a year ago, Wagner,
сеча если бы е там год назад го Вагнер
it would have sounded somehow, you know, there, when
это ещ как-то бы знаешь там звучало при
Prigozhin was alive, now
живом пригожине сейчас
Wagner, Who is
Вагнер Кто такой
Wagner, no one is
Вагнер какая-то никому не
interested, show me another chevron, come on, show me
интересно покажи ещё шеврон давай покажи
chevron skeleton with a violin
шеврон скелет со скрипкой
forgot
забыли
said but he is not he is alive
сказал а он не он живой
Yes
Да
hung up and you also will not just say that
навешали и ты также не просто скажут что
you are
ты
alive damn
живой блин
what really huge respect to you you
какие реально вам огромный респект вы
raised my spirits so much I am looking for a roulette
мне так подняли настроение Я щет рулетку
here some you know just boring
тут какие-то знаешь просто скучные
types
типы
Volunteers
Добровольцы
Volunteers chevron Bye
Добровольцы шеврон Пока покажи ещё раз
show me the chevron What kind of
шеврон Покажи мне шеврон Что за
shyness Come on chevron
стеснялся Давай шеврон
show come on show chevron show chevron
покажи
you only show Show me I'll show you come on
те только покажет Покажи шь я тебе
show on ko come on bye Come on
покажу давай покажи на ко давай пока
ran away let's do it normally
убежал давайте нормально
remember come on Here come on with the
пом давай Вот давай при
account exactly Yes exactly and what kind of
сч точно Так точно а какой род
troops airborne troops
войск ВДВ
airborne Yes you are cool
десант Да вы круты
What are you going to do
Что собираетесь делать контракт
sign a contract Cool yeah Cool yeah
подписывать Прикольно да Прикольно да
there you are in short paratroopers like flies need to be
там ти короче десантники как мухи надо
replenished
пополнять
fill up Well we'll see some more And what regiment are you from What regiment do you have there what do you have We have this there
полнять Ну посмотрим ещё А вы с какого
what Ryazan school
да там вот это что Рязанское училище
stupidly in short there are already no graduates left alive
тупо короче уже всё не осталось в живых
at all funny How do
выпускников вообще ржака
you know we know  we watch reports, we
Ты откуда знаешь знаем сводки смотрим
watch your news, I subscribe to groups
смотрю новости ваши я подписан на группы
like where the paratroopers and their wives are there, they
типа где десантники и ихние жёны там
drop off who died and so on. There's
скидывают там кто погиб и так далее Там
just you. Well,
просто вас Ну
such a Usan. Yes, yes, we're in politics, no, we do
такое такая усан Да да мы ж в политике
n't influence, I'm not you, well, they'll send
не не не влияем я не вы ну пошлют
you, but you want. Why do you want to talk? We're talking
вас а хотите Почему хотите пообщаться мы
about war. So what's unclear about the war? The
о войне Так а что тут о войне неясно
West gives weapons that kill, your
даёт э Запад оружие которым убивают ваши
planes, your boats, in short, and in general, everyone is against
самолёты ваши короче лодки и вообще всем
you.
на вас
Nobody but us.
же Никто кроме нас
Airborne troops, you know,
Воздушный десант понимаешь
brother, they're funny.
брат смешные
What regions
а вы сами с каких регионов
were you from? I'm from Samara, and the second one is
были я с Самары а второй
from Vladikavkaz.
а второй с Владикавказа
Ossetian. Ossetian. Yes, it's
осетин осетин
cool, Ingush. Hello, Ingush. Hello, Ingush.
Да прикольно ингушам Привет ингушам
Salam. And who are you by nationality? I'm
привет ингушам салам А ты кто по нации я
Ingush. I'm
Ингуш я
Ingush. And why are you?
ингуш А почему ты
Why Ukraine? Because the Ingush. We are for
а почему Украину потому что ингуши Мы за
Ukraine and against those who drove
Украину и против этих которые изгнали
us out of the Caucasus from the suburban
нас с лоди Кавказа с пригородного
area. And now, nothing, nothing,
района И что теперь ничего топи ниче
Ukrainians. Why are there so many Ingush,
украинцев почему очень много ингушей
Chechens, Caucasus, fighting against Putin's
чеченцев Кавказ воюют против путинских
Putin because  what look Putin what Putin
Путин потому что смотри Путин что Путин
did to our
сделал с нашими
people what Putin did to the peoples of the
народами что сделал с Путин с народами
Caucasus
Кавказа
Yeah and how Putin robs our
Ага а как Путин грабит наши
regions You look at your Samara
регионы Ты посмотри на свою самарскую
region I was in
область Я был в
Samara and was in Moscow you saw how they live
Самаре и был в Москве ты видел как живут
in Moscow and how in Samara how in Samara Yes he knows
в Москве и как в Самаре как в Самаре Да
look Why Moscow takes
знает знат смотри Почему Москва забирает
from all the regions from my Ingushetia from your
со всех регионов с моей ингушети с твоей
Samara region yes takes the money and
Самарской области да забирает бабло и
builds itself si tars in short all sorts of things there
строят си тары короче всякие там у нас
tell me they can't figure us out on this chat roulette at
скажи нас по этой чатрулетке вычислить
all Who can figure out here like
могут вообще не Кто тут сможет вычислить
us Interesting I
типа нам Интересно
just don't know maybe some special services
просто не знаю может какая-то спецслужб
and figure me out they didn't
и вычисляют меня не
figure me out and what else did those Russians say
вычисляли и что те русские ещё говорили
when they met
когда встречались с
you asked they
тобой спрашивал
live poor America in
бедно живут Америка в
America cars computers the Armed Forces are American
Америке машины компьютеры ВС американско
and Russia is poor
а Россия бедная
poverty only they take everything Yes they
нища только всё забирают Да Москву
made Moscow Like a picture Putin had everything
сделали Как картинку у Путина всё было
good and in Samara your parents live in
хорошо а в Самаре вот твои родители в
Samara
Самаре
Well yes mom
живут Ну да мама
[music]
[музыка]
works okay come on come on No who
работает да ладно давай давай Да не кем
mom works I know salaries  I want to
мама работает я знаю зарплаты Я хочу
understand what mom works as, yes,
понять кем мама работает да нормальные у
we have normal salaries in Russia, who does mom work as?
нас зарплаты в России кем мамка работает
Why are you embarrassed? Why are you embarrassed?
Почему ты стесняешься Почему ты
What difference does it make who mom
стесняешься Да какая разница кем ма
sees? You're even embarrassed by who Mom
видишь ты даже стесняешься кем Мама
works for, mom is a job. Yes, I just don't
работает мама рабо жесть Да просто не
want to talk. I mean, I don't want to. What's the
хочу говорить В смысле не хочу Ну что ту
matter? It's not a crime to say where
такое Это же не преступление сказать где
mom
мама
works. As a doctor, as a teacher, as a doctor,
работает Медиком учителем кем Медиком
as a teacher, Yes, that's all
учителем кем учителем учителем Да всё у
he has, his salary is that he, a
него зарплата ц у него
teacher, can buy himself a car, damn, in
учитель может себе купить машину блин за
six months. Your mom's job has been
полгода Работа твоя мамка за 20 лет
working at
работае в
school for 20 years, it's not about money, brother, but about their
школе не в деньгах брат счастья а в их
quantity. Yes, their quantity. Yes, you know, I'll
количестве Да их количест Да знаешь я
tell you this: When they say in America
тебе вот что скажу когда в Америке
that strength is in money and in Truth, both
говорят что сила и в деньгах и в Правде
truth and money are needed. And in Russia,
нужна и правда и деньги А в России
Moscow takes the money for itself and
Москва себе забирает деньги а регионам
tells the regions that strength is not in money but in truth. As
говорит сила не в деньгах а в правде в
a result, in the regions, there is no truth or money. There is no
результате в регионах Ни правды ни денег
truth or money. Is it true
нет Ни правды ни денег Это что правда
that your mom, who
что твоя мама да которая горбатий
studied hunchbacked, Why do hunchbacked people
училась Почему горбатий на на работах
get such a small salary at work now,
сейчас получают такую маленькую зарплату
and Muscovites are living the high life.
а москвичи жируют
Moscow was a war before the war, and before the war, what?
Моск война до войны а до войны что
Muscovites in short received like your mother
москвичи короче получали как твоя мамка
your mother your mother She is no worse than some
твоя мама твоя мама Она не хуже какой-то
glamorous daughter of a deputy from
гламурной дочки депутата из
Moscow Why do deputy's daughters give a yacht a
Москвы Почему дочки депутата дают яхту
yacht instead of giving your mother a
яхту вместо того чтобы твоей маме
car like that Yes, bro, I don't know about these things
машину вот так Да братан я в этих делах
And how do you think why your
не шарю А как ты думаешь почему твоя
mother
мамка бедно
lives poorly Yes, how should I know
живёт Да я откуда знаю
why Well, I mean, she's look, she's not
почему Ну то есть она же смотри она ж не
stupid Yes, she's smart, she raised you Yes, she
глупая Да Умная она тебя воспитала Да
lives poorly How is it that in a
жит бедно Как так получается что в
country where oil, gas, diamonds, everyone
стране в которой нефть газ алмазы всего
lives poorer Than in countries
живёт беднее Чем в странах
Why let's
Почему давай
think let's talk Well, look, if
подумаем давай пооб Ну смотри если
for example people live in the Czech Republic where there is no
например люди живут в Чехии в которой
gas, oil, diamonds and they live richer
нет газа нефти алмазов и живут богаче
than in Samara How does it happen how does it
чем в Самаре Как так получается как так
happen No, tell me how is it
получается Нет ты мне скажи как так
that Zelensky first dances in KVN
получается что Зеленский сначала в КВН
and then becomes president of
танцует а потом президентом становится
Ukraine Look, Zelensky dances in KVN and
украи смотри Зеленский танцует в КВН
becomes president like Tut on
становится президентом как Вт на
your mother's salary and
зарплату твоей мамы и
you already about your mother Okay, look, I'll
тебя про маму уже Хорошо смотри я
explain I heard by the way such a
объясню то слышал кстати такой вот
Russian volunteer
русский добровольческий
corps  Let's talk in short, not about money already,
корпус Давай короче не о деньгах уже
Dava, not about money, about meanings, I heard the
Дава не о деньгах о смыслах слышал
Russian volunteer corps, the Legion of
русский добровольческий корпус Легион
Freedom of Russia, there is
Свобода росссии
no way, look, Kolya, the
никак есть смотри Коли
Legion of Freedom of Russia, the Siberian battalion, there are a
Легион Свобода России Сибирский батальон
lot of Russians now, Yes, they are rebelling
сейчас очень много русских Да восстают
against Putin, in the Belgorod region,
против Путина вот в Белгородской области
they have already captured part of the territory, expelled all sorts of FSB officers from there, and a lot of people are going over to the side of these rebels, Let's talk heart to heart, just talk heart to heart, I'm saying, Look, really heart to heart, These are the people, I respect them, these are the Russians who have rebelled against Putin, and many, many will join them, they are
они
speaking out, not they are speaking out for your mother to vote for Putin, you
выступают не они выступают за то чтобы
know,
проголосовала знае твоя мамка голосовала
your mother voted for Putin, your mother voted
Путина твоя мамка голосовала
for the whole regiment, they voted, And how were you
за всем полком голосовали А как вас
brought to the
привели на
vote, how could you,
голосование
Well, if you voted not
как А ты мог Вот если ты проголосовал не
for Putin, but so that it would be
за Путина а чтобы тебе было было
nothing for you, so how will you prove that you
ничего так А как ты докажешь что Ты
voted for Putin, Tina, I mean, how will I
голосовал за Путина Тина В смысле как я
prove it, Well, you said that you voted
докажу Ну ты сказал что ты проголосовал
for  Putin Maybe you can
за Путина Может ты
cheat like I cheat or something I look like a
обману как я обманываю я что что ли
soldier That is, you don't believe me yes I don't
солдат То есть ты мне не веришь да
believe it good but look
не верю не верю хорошо а вот смотри
Why did you vote for Putin Look
Почему ты голосовал за Путина Вот смотри
Putin rules born in such a year
Путин правит такого года рождения такого
born in such a year about 20 years ago
года рождения где-то лет 20 назад
ninety-four Yes ninety or
девяносто четвёртого Да девяносто неже
ninety-five ninety-sixth day
девяносто пятого девяносто шестого дено
yes yes although don't wait 20 for which I
да да хотя не подожди 20 за что я как
counted
посчитал
2005 what year are you How old are you the
2005 какого ты года Сколько тебе лет
second year
второго года
2002 yes that is look you were born Putin
2002 да то есть смотри ты родился Путин
was already president
уже был президентом
president Well yes that is you grew up you
президентом Ну да то есть ты вырос ты
grew up stupidly in the Putin era and now
рос тупо в эпоху Путина и теперь
look You see that your mother and you
смотри Ты видишь что твоя мама и ты
live live in poverty you generally seem to have a
живут живёте в бедности ты вообще походу
voice I'm telling you I voted for Putin
голосу Я тебе говорю я за Путина
because he's a beauty I understand
проголосовал потому что он Красава понял
you
ты слышал такую
heard such a group Sektor
слышал группу Сектор
Gaza of course I heard there they have a
Газа конечно слышал там у них есть
good song
хорошая песня
utilization Yes I
утилизация Да я
heard
слышал
utilization That's in short yes I thought
утилизация Вот это короче да я думал
to get through to your brain but it's impossible
Достучаться к твоему мозгу но невозможно
to get through to  emptiness is
Достучаться в пустоту
unrealistic only
нереально только
disposal take off mute what to talk about
утилизация сни нема про что говорить
hello gonta situation a year already
здравствуй гонта положение год уже
let's have a normal conversation
давайте нормально пообщаемся
eat a year a year they treat me a year who are people
ешь год год на меня лечат год кто люди
let's Oh my favorite this is a flag the most
давай О мой любимый это прапор самый
awesome flag in my life Lithuania this is the
обалденный прапор в моей жизни Литва это
flag of Lithuania who the hell did I throw this banner down and just trample on it from Lithuania This is the flag of
топтал из лит Это флаг
Lithuania
Литвы
Why is Lithuania a normal country Lithuania is a
Это почему Литва нормальная страна Литва
Russian village what
- это русская деревня ты
are you And why are you insulting like that and why
что А ты зачем оскорбляешь так и А зачем
but
но пере
translations Lithuania is a village or
вки Литва это деревня или
not your version Lithuania is a Russian
нет ваше версии Литва - это русская
village Girl do you
деревня Девушка вы так
agree
согласны
no Why do you speak Russian Without an
нет Вы почему на русском говорите Без
accent dasta how did this
акцента даста как это так
happen my father is Belarusian my mother is Lithuanian
случилось у меня отец Беларус мама
I grew up nanny my
литовка Я вырос
dad is Ukrainian my mother is Russian what
ня меня папа украи мама русская я что
should I speak Ukrainian
должна говорить
Lithuania Lithuania is not a
по-украински Литва Литва это не
statehood it is not a nation it is
государственность это не нация это
Russian it is a village of Russia well he is talking
русская это деревня России ну он разго
small like that So what from a spikelet So
маленькая такая вот Ну и что от колосок
what well speaking Russian is
Ну и что ну разговаривать по-русски
good and how is he where is he from  knows Russian
хорошо и как он откуда он знает русский
because he is Russian by
язык потому что он русский сам по
nationality he knows Russians all Russian
национальности он знает русские все
everyone knows an international language yes
русский все знают международный язык да
international you yourself speak
международный ты сам говоришь
international yk Well it is clear there in
международный ык Ну понятно там в
America they speak there in China
Америке там разговаривают там в Китай
there where there well Lithuania is a village
там где там ну Литва - это деревня
Russian Lithuania for you a village Estonia a
Русская Литва для тебя деревня Эстония
village is good but they know Russian The
деревня хорошо но они знают русский язык
Baltics are Russian they are all
Прибалтика это русски они все
Russian-speaking There they are all refugees there in
русскоязычные Там они все беженцы туда в
Russian villages they speak Russian to everyone
русских деревнях на всех на русских
what do you want to order
говорят что ты хочешь заказать
humiliate I want to humiliate him I myself
унизить хочу его унизить Я сам из
grew up in a Russian
русской деревни вырос в русской
village orbi him Yes I tell him what so what the
дерев орби его Да я его говорю
check speaks to you
что ну и что чек с тобой разговаривает
in Russian what is
по-русски что
bad va What is your name
плохо ва Как вас зовут
girl and me Ira Inya is very pretty
девушка а меня Ира Иня очень симпатично
MRKO to call
МРКО
here is the first husband know I love this
звать вот первой мужа зна Я люблю это
name Andrey madly you celebrated February 14
имя Андрей безумно вы 14 февраля
You will not believe My
отмечали Вы не поверите У меня девушка
first girlfriend was Irina also such warm
первая была Ирина тоже такие тёплые
Memories it is just like between
Воспоминания это просто это как между
us you know connection right with me
нами знаете коннекшн прям у меня вот
honestly my my child was born from
честно мой мой ребёнок рождённый от
Andrey and I have no more children  I am
Андрея и больше у меня нет детей у меня
the smartest child in this world from
самый умный ребёнок на этом свете от
Andre did you don't care what I did
Андре сделала тебя не волнует что я
what I didn't do Maybe I didn't do anything at all
сделала что я не делала Может я вообще
who is this man what is he how badly he
кто вот этот мужчина что он как он плохо
treats you who is he to you at all nobody
к вам относится он кто вообще вам он нам
nobody understood Well yes then this nobody Let him continue to
никто никто понял Ну да тогда этот никто
drink And we
Пусть все дальше бухает А мы с вами
will talk with you Irina look Irina
Ирина поговорим смотрите Ирина он
of course he doesn't respect you a little since he
конечно немножко не уважает вас раз так
says so you know how much you have
говорит знаете там сколько ты
done even if you did it is your
сдела даже если бы и делали это ваше
personal business what does he have to do with it not only sticking
личное дело причём он тут не то что суёт
his nose in yet In front of other men he
свой нос ещё При других мужчинах это
says this so it is very much to me about
говорит так это коне очень мне каже про
nevos this is such a thing and by
невос это такое есть а вы
the way you are so right because not
кстати настолько прав потому что не
only you are talking about it many
только вы об этом говорите уже много
people already even my friends are talking about it
людей даже мои подруги об этом говорят
that why slu And why are you together with him
что почему слу А почему вы тогда с ним
now I can't howl my
вместе сейчас я не могу выть свое
apartment
квартиры
why doesn't he
почему он не
leave you know what he tells me in a
уходит знаешь что мне говорит через
week I will leave
неделю уйду я выстав
him these belongings and he doesn't leave What are you talking about call the
его эти пожитки а он не уходит Что ты
police what is the
несёшь полицию вызвать в чём
problem that you are pushing me and the police that is why a
проблема что ты меня толкаешь а
woman is pushing you yes I
полицию поэтому тебя женщина толкает да
didn't think about the police By the way oh well By the way
о полиции не подумала Кстати а ну Кстати
I didn't think about the police  thought
о полиции я не подумала
Andryusha ichka Push him again Once let him in
Андрюша ичка Толкни его ещ Раз пусть он
short coffee you sweat sde Dava floor
короче кофе тебе пот сде Дава пол
Ira says Go Come on in short everything you
Ира говорит Пошёл Давай короче всё теб
girl pushes you you for
девушка тебя толкает ты для
not Go make coffee for her in short Ira Yeah
не Иди сделай кофе ей короче Ира Ага
now he ran up to make coffee And what
сейчас разбежался на делать кофе А что
he won't do Make coffee for
он не сделает Кофе
someone understood he's like that
сделай кому-нибудь понял он такой
Turn the camera on yourself a little I want
Поверни на себя камеру немножко Я хочу
you completely Vit you're very cute
тебя полностью Вить ты очень симпати
butchka I'm not pretty of course now just
мучка Я некрасивая конечно сейчас просто
Nekra normal Listen you have forms in
Некра нормально Слушай у тебя формы есть
short you have forms Irochka Yes
короче формы есть у тебя Ирочка Да у
I have a form these are jugs you're cool you're cool
меня форма это крынки ты классная ты
Sparta Spartan brigade
класная Спарта Бригада
awesome
спартанка офигенная
basements And you look at the
подвалах А ты смотри на
machine gunner What city are you from ich
пулемётчика Ты из какого города
look
ич смотри
at There you need a battery how we will leave you now Yes give me the charger I say will leave I
на Там батарейка нужна как мы вас сейчас
say give me the
Да дай зарядку говорю уйдёт говорю дай
charger they were called charger
зарядку их называли зарядку
look he will switch now he will
смотри он сейчас переключит он
switch
переключит
not
не
attention there Come on bring the charger
внимание сть Давай зарядку приноси
Come on run bring the charger Zarya ethos switch
давай бегом Принеси Заря этос переключи
Samara Russia  runner Cool
Самара Россия полоз Прикольно А сейчас
Where are you now Where are you from I'm from Kyiv Where are you now
где А ты откуда Я из Киева А ты сейчас
z by place I understood
где з по месту понял
contract soldier What topics do you talk about on the
контрактник На какие темы общаетесь на
topic of
тему
war not Streamer pi
войны не Стример пи
just talking Today we have tomorrow it turns
просто общаюсь Сегодня у нас же завтра
out 3 years since
будет получается 3 года как Война
Full-scale war is going on so I decided to go out and
полномасштабная идёт вот решил выйти
ask Russians what do you think about
поспрашивать россиян что вы думаете об
it every war is
этом каждая война - это
bad Well, why did you go to
плохо Ну а ты зачем пошёл на
war And who
войну А кто на кого
attacked whom Well, America against Russia What is your
напал Ну Америка на Россию Как тебя
name How can I say goodbye to you Andrey
зовут Как я могу тебя прощаться Андрей
Andrey
Андрей
Andrey well, well, it's not for you and me to decide that's right
Андрей ну ну не нам с тобой решать вот
But we I can't talk to
да Но мы я не могу поговорить с
politicians Yes, I only watch them on TV
политиками Да я только их по телевизору
and with ordinary people I'm a simple
смотрю а с простыми людьми вот я простой
person I can talk to ordinary people Well,
человек с простыми людьми могу
I wonder what you
разговаривать Ну мне интересно как вы
think We are one people, it's true and we fight
думаете Мы же один народ правда и воюем
Why are we fighting Why did you go to kill
Почему мы воюем Почему вы пошли убивать
people What year were you born in
людей Ты какого года рождения
eighty-
восемьдесят
first And you, you look very good I do
первого А ты ты очень выглядишь
n't drink And what year were you born in ninety Well, yes,
не бухаю а ты какого года девяностого Ну
look They told us that Well, we jumped too much there they said to
да смотри Нам сказали то Ну допрыгались
hang someone there and that's
там сказали гиляку там вот это
all Well, yes, we jumped, wait, where did they say where they
всё Ну да прыгали вы подожди а где
shouted at
говорили где кричали на
Gilyaku on
гиляку на
this went in Kiev
этом шело в кие
Maidan understand look if in Kyiv on
Майдане понять смотри если в Киеве на
Maidan they shouted at Gilyaku And why
Майдане кричали на гиляку А зачем Россия
then Russia bombs and destroys Russian-speaking
тогда бомбит и уничтожает русскоязычные
cities Bakhmut there Kharkov
города бахмут там Харьков
Mariupol Well you want Russia to
Мариуполь Ну ты хочешь чтобы Россия
start destroying Kyiv Well I just
начала уничтожать Киев Ну я просто я
thought look The thing is that if
думал смотри Дело в том что если скакали
Russian troops were jumping on Maidan in Kyiv howling troops
на Майдане в Киеве российские вой войска
went to Kyiv what to take I jumped Yes I
пошли на Киев что взять ыл я прыгал Да я
jumped who with who with yes yes
прыгал кто с кто
then why look why did you leave
с да да то зачем смотри зачем вы ушли
Kyiv with troops and destroy
войсками из-под Киева а уничтожили
Bakhmut in Bakhmut no one jumped and
бахмут в бахмуте никто не прыгал и не
shouted at Gilyaku And in Mariupol and in
кричал на гиляку А в Мариуполе и в
Mariupol no one shouted at Gilyaku And you
Мариуполе никто не кричал на гиляку А вы
bombed it and in rtos too no one
его бомбили а в ртос тоже никто не
shouted just look only in Kyiv in
кричал только смотри только в Киеве в
Kyiv they shouted at Gilyaku on Maidan do
Киеве кричали на гиляку на Майдане
you want
хочешь чтобы
Kyiv Well why did you capture Kyiv overthrow
Киев Ну зачем захватили Киев скинули
Zelensky and that's it You want Kyiv to
Зеленского и всё Ты хочешь чтобы Киев
be like Mariupol Well I just
был похож на Мариуполь Ну так Я просто
don't understand you  if you were jumping on the Maidan And
не понимаю вас если скакали на Майдане А
you destroyed Mariupol and not the Maidan in
вы уничтожили Мариуполь а не Майдан в
Kyiv Andryu okay do
Киеве Андрю ладно
n't give it to the point Yes, to the point How are you
не давай по делу Да ж по делу Как вы
going to win if Kyiv is not
собираетесь победить если Киев не
captured Yes, we will have to capture it and
захватить Да захватим надо будет и
cure it Well, look, you were near Kiev and
вылечим его Ну смотри вы были под Киевом
ran away and then destroyed Bakhmut
убежали а дальше уничтожили бахмут
Why did we take Bakhmut, so why were
Зачем бахмут же взяли мы так зачем там
n't the people there jumping on the Maidan They were
не скакали на Майдане люди Они были
against the Maidan The people in Bakhmut were
против Майдана люди в бахмуте были
against the Maidan Well, your troops were there,
против Майдан Ну ваши войска там были
that's right And why did you attack
так правильно А вы зачем напали на
Bakhmut They would have attacked Kyiv there too, troops
бахмут напали бы на Киев там тоже войска
and they were jumping on the Maidan Wait, wait,
и там скакали на Майдане Подожди подожди
gradually, wait, we will come So you were already there,
постепенно это подожди придём мы Так вы
you already came to Kyiv Why did
уже были вы уже ж пришли под Киев зачем
you
вы
leave It was a deceptive maneuver It was a deceptive maneuver to
ушли обманный манёвр
leave
был обманный манёвр уйти из
Kyiv No, they
Киева нет
came Vaska They
пришли Васька
deceived a tactical move And what
обманули тактический ход А в чём этот
was this tactical move, that they deceived I can't
тактический ход был что обманули не могу
understand I'm not a military man I just don't
понять Я не военный просто не
know how they deceived Well, if you are ri
шарю как это обманули Ну если ты ри
then don't go there  Well, they put so many special forces
тогда и не лезь туда Ну столько спецназа
in Gostomel, not you just
положили в гостомеле своего не ты только
now said, you then You're climbing there Well,
сейчас сказал ты тогда Туда лезешь ну
I'm just looking I don't understand why you
просто я смотрю Я не понимаю зачем вы
ran away from
убежали из-под
Kyiv You're not a military man then don't climb there
Киева ты не военный тогда не лезь туда
Well, I
ну
wonder And from Kherson Why did you
интересно А из Херсона Зачем
run away Okay, no, don't climb there Well,
убежали ладно не это не лезь тудай
look, Russians Russians ran away
из Ну смотри русские русские убежали
from Kyiv, from Kherson, from Kharkov
из-под Киева из Херсона из-под Харькова
Why, so what kind of deceptive Man Zaporizhzhya,
Почему так что за обманный Ман запорож
something like a lot for deceptive maneuvers
что-то много за обманный манёвров
Yes, they ran away Well, what next And how could the
Да убежали Ну дальше что А по как могла
Russian army, so powerful, run away
Российская армия такая мощнейшая убежать
from a small Ukrainian
от маленькой украинской
Yes, they ran away, how was it, why did they
Да убежали как было почему
run away, they didn't cope, I understand And why in
убежали не справились понял А почему в
said this was a tactical move, I understood And in the
сказал это тактический ход понял а в
Kursk region there was also a tactical move to
Курской области тоже был тактический ход
run away and leave part of the Kursk region to
убежать и оставить часть Курской области
Ukraine
Украине
Yes And what is the tactic I just don't know these
да А в чём тактика Я просто не шарю эти
things If you don't know then
дела Если ты нери тог
What is the tactical move to give part of
В чём тактический ход отдать часть
Russia to the enemy
России
climb there If you're not a military man
врагу лезь туда если ты не не военный
If you don't know Well, on the contrary, I
Если ты не шаришь Ну так наоборот
wonder
интересно
[laughter]
[смех]
Well, what kind of deceptive  maneuver So listen
Ну какие обманные манёвр Так слушайте
Russian I give you a topic make a deceptive
русский я вам даю тему сделайте обманный
HP lure the Ukrainian army to the Kremlin
НР замани украинскую армию под Кремль
so that the Ukrainian army comes to Red
чтоб украинская армия пришла на Красную
Square and then That's the
Площадь а потом
topic lure yes let Zelensky
Вот это тема замани да пусть Зеленский
make a parade on Red Square And
делает парад на Красной Площади А
you like a squeak comment a letter on my
вы лайк писка комент пись на мий
Telegram right now axis VN and
Telegram прям зараз ось ВН а
Popik this is very and very important YouTube is
Попик це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube
busy with us through scarg Orks in your ban and
заня нас через скарг Орки в твый бан и
very many videos I do not show to people
дуже багато видео не показую людям
at times I do not show information about streams so that
вчасно не показуе информация про стримы
we Mali operational
тому для того щоб ми Мали оперативный
links are written right now and Popik there
звязок пишиться прямо зараз а Попик там
in Telegram OKM video also interesting and
в телегра окм вдео ще теж цикава и
useful information and we are sorry with you
корисна информация и ми повинни з вами
constant operational links
тримати постийний оперативный звязок
independently in that will show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Glory to Ukraine letter
YouTube Слава Украине пись
L
L